It is Space History Alpha Year 58823.
＜わずかに残った人類は
地球によく似た惑星→
The small fraction of humanity that remains
クリーン４６４９の
領有権をかけて→
spend their days fighting a never-ending
日々終わることのない争いを
続けていた…＞
battle over possession of Kleen,
a planet similar to Earth.
（爆発音）
（アバター：城山）お母ちゃ～ん！
Mommy!
（アバター：夏目）あはは　城ちゃん
派手に逝っちゃったね。
Shiro-chan sure blasted off with a bang...
（アバター：神崎）なんて分厚い弾幕だ！
What heavy curtain fire!
（アバター：古市）
テレビを　ご覧の皆さん
ここは戦場の真っ只中！
Dear TV viewers, I'm coming to
you from the center of a warzone!
焔王チームと
オンラインゲーム対戦中なのです。
We're in the middle of fighting
Team Enoh in an online game!
この勝負に勝てば　焔王の居場所を教えてもらえるというのですが…。
If we win this battle, Lord En
will tell us where he is, but...
えっ！？
（爆発音）
うわ～っ！！
（アバター：千秋）寧々さん　急いで！
Nene-san, quickly.
（アバター：寧々）
ていうか私　前回やられたんじゃ
なかったっけ？
Wait, wasn't I killed the last episode?
あれは単に　今回へのヒキです。
That was just to draw people
to watch the next episode.
それに私　衛生兵ですから
蘇生可能ですし。
And besides, I'm a medic,
I can resuscitate you.
せっかく感動的に終われると
思ったのに…うっ。
Aw, I thought I'd had such
an emotional farewell...
（キャタピラ音）
あれは！？
（アバター：ヨルダ）
オーッホッホッホッ！
もはや勝ったも同然ですわ。
That's...
Our victory is all but assured!
さあ　おとなしく
戦車の餌食になりなさい！
Now, become food for this tank!
くっ…。
えええええ！？
イヤーッ！！
（アバター：由加）
寧々さ～ん！ちょ～デカいロボ
見つけちゃいました！
Nene-san!
I found me a crazy big robot!
おい…。
（古市）
な～んか世界観　ぶっ壊れてね？
Um, doesn't that ruin the world building?
Super Burning Combination
アハハ！踏み潰しまっせ～！
Gotta crush 'em all!
何なのよ　これは！
What the hell is that?
１／２５６の確率で出てくる
激レアマシン→
It's the Crazy Frog, an extremely rare
mech with a 1/256 chance of appearing!
クレイジーフロッグだ。
でかしたぞ　花澤！
Nice going, Hanazawa!
（アバター：由加）
ドライブシュートだぁ～！
Drive and... shoot!
ぎょ～っ！！
（アバター：由加）
見たか！マジ　パネェっしょ！
You see that? It was so crazy!
（由加）ハハハ！パネェ！
このゲーム　楽しいっスね。
Crazy! This game's a blast!
（神崎）
バカ！パー子　油断してっと！
Idiot! Don't let your guard down, crazy!
（爆発音）
うわ～っ！！
着弾確認！
（アバター：イザベラ）第二射　急げ。
Direct hit, confirmed.
Hurry with the second round!
（アバター：焔王）第二射　急げ～！
《この子　邪魔…》
Hurry with the second round!
This kid's in the way...
ん？…あっ！
やったな　コノヤロー！→
Now you've done it, you bastards!
ゆかち～キーック！！
Yukachi Kick!
（アバター：焔王）ギャーッ！！
（アバター：イザベラ）離れないで下さい
坊っちゃま！！
Stay close to me, Master!
ハハハ！ゆかち～…→
Yukachi... tap dance!
タップダーンス！
ほれ～　ほれ　ほれ～！
悪のりしすぎだぞ　パー子。
Crazy bitch is goin' way overboard!
《いやいや…いけるぞ　これ！→
No wait, this might work...
何せ負けたら街ごと火の海だから
ビビリまくってたけど…→
I was shaking like a leaf that we'd lose and
the city'd be engulfed in a sea of fire,
ナイス！パー澤さん！→
but you go, Crazyzawa-san!
これなら勝てる！》
This way... we can win!
（ピーピーピー…）
Mine
あっ…。
あ？
地雷～！！
え～っ！？
A mine?!
（爆発音）
てへっ！
（姫川）てへっじゃね～よ！このパー子！！→
"Tee-hee" my ass, you crazy bitch!
あれが　どんだけ貴重な武器かわかってんのか！！
Do you have any idea how
crucial that weapon was?
（夏目）
まあまあ　とりあえず目障りな戦車も片付けたし　これからでしょ。
Now now... At least we got rid of those
annoying tanks. The real battle begins now, right?
で　ですよね～
さすが夏目先輩！
T-Totally! You tell 'em, Natsume-senpai!
（千秋）
そうです　冷静になって下さい。
振り出しに戻っただけです。→
Correct. Everyone calm down.
We're simply back to how we started.
それに寧々さんが乗ってたら
私達まで踏み潰されてましたよ。
（寧々）私のことはいいでしょ！
And if you'd been driving it, Nene-san,
we'd have been crushed as well.
Was that necessary?!
奴らめ～！許さん　許さんぞ！
Those bastards! Unforgivable!
Totally unforgivable!
イザベラ　早く奴らを
ギャフンと言わすのじゃ！
Isabella, hurry up and show them what for!
仰せの通りに。
おイタの過ぎた者どもに→
As you wish, I will show these
rambunctious pranksters true hell.
本当の地獄を見せてやりますわ。
《ていうか　ギャフンて…》
《今どき言わないよな…》
Uh, "what for"?
Nobody says that any more...
♪～（ラジオ）
（早乙女）
よう　てめえら！歯磨いたか？
Hey, you jerks! Brushed those teeth?
禅十郎さんだ。
修業だって楽しくなくっちゃな。
I'm Mr. Zenjuro, and I'm hear to tell
you that training's gotta be fun!
ってことで　今日は俺と一緒に
レッツ魔力解放！
（ベル坊）アイアイヤー！
So now then, together with me...
Let's Unleash Our Magic Power!
ヘーイ　ヘーイ！ワンツーさんし！いつまでたっても成長期　ハイッ！
Hey, hey! One two three four...
Always growing up! Now you!
（男鹿）いつまでたっても成長期！
Always growing up!
アッ　ダブー！
次は腕を前に　ムカつく奴の前歯を叩き折る運動だ！
Next, put your arms up and break the teeth
of the annoying bastard in front of you!
ヘーイ　ヘーイ　ワンツーさんし！
ごめん　お前ら砕け散れ　ハイ！
Hey, hey! One two three four...
Sorry, but bite the dust! Now you!
ごめん　お前ら砕け散れ！
Sorry, but bite the dust.
いいね　いいね～！クソッタレどもそれじゃあ次は！
次はじゃねえ！！
Nice, you pieces of crap.
Now then, next...
Next nothing!
ヘイヘーイ！何をするんだ男鹿隊員？ハイ！
Hey, hey... What are you doing, Recruit Oga?
Now you.
だから　これのどこが修業なんだよエクササイズじゃね～んだぞ！！
How is this training at all?!
It's just exercise!
（早乙女）
エクササイズ？
おいおい　失礼なこと言ってっと→
Exercise?
Hold it... Insult me and I'll blast
you out beyond the milky way.
銀河系の外まで　ぶっ飛ばすぞ。
これは三日三晩ぐっすり寝て→
This is my super effective program
I just thought up on the fly
さっき適当に思いついた
強化プログラムだぜ。
適当すぎんだろ！！
after sleeping straight
for 3 days and nights!
Damn straight it's on the fly!
男鹿…お前　よろしくお願いしますつったよなあ？→
Oga... I'm pretty sure you said you'd do it.
だったら
つべこべ言ってんじゃね～よ！→
So no bitchin'!
やるのか？やらね～のか？
Are you gonna do it, or not?!
アイタタ　アイアイアイアアーイ！
だ～っ！わかったよ！
やりゃいいんだろ　やりゃあ！！
Fine, I get the picture!
I just have to do it, right?
よ～し　それじゃあ次は　腹から
胸にかけてのエクササイズだ！
Next up is an exercise that'll work
your stomach up to your chest!
って　自分でエクササイズって
言っちゃったよ　おい。
You just called it exercise yourself...
レッツ　ダンシング！
Let's Dancing!
油断しないで下さい。敵も戦車を失った以上　ゲリラ戦術で…。
Don't let your guard down. Without their
tank, they've turned to guerrilla warfare.
何？
あ　いえ　何か気配がしたような。
What?
No... I thought I sensed something...
気配？敵が近づいて来たら
マップに表示されるんでしょ？
Sensed? But if there's an enemy near,
they'll show up on the map, right?
《何もないところから！？》
Who shot that?!
（爆発音）
（城山）うわ～っ！！
どうしたの？城ちゃん。や　やられた…突然現れた
チェーンソーで真っ二つに～！
What's the matter, Shiro-chan?
I-I'm done for! Split in two by
a chainsaw that just appeared!
こりゃ　画面見せられないね。
Well, we can't show that...
一体　何が？
チートか…。
What in the world...
Cheating?
チート？
引きこもりの事っスか？
Cheats?
You mean like, NEETs?
（姫川）オンラインゲームで
最も忌み嫌われる行為だ。→
It's the most despised thing
people do in online games.
こいつら　ゲームのプログラム
自体を不正に改造してやがる。
They've changed the programming
of the game itself.
光学迷彩なんて
このゲームにはねえぞ。
This game doesn't have
optical camouflage in it.
こ　光学迷彩…。
Optical camouflage?
（姫川）
奴ら　姿も見えずレーダーにも
映らねえ透明人間になりやがった。
They've turned themselves invisible
and they can't be seen on radar.
敵を確認できないなんて
どうやって倒せばいいんですか？
If we can't see them, how can we beat them?
（姫川）城山　ちょっと代わってろ。
Shiroyama... Switch with me for a bit.
（城山）
お　おい　姫川　どこへ行く？
Wait, Himekawa... Where are you going?
１０分ほど持ちこたえてろ。
その間に用意する。
Hold out for 10 minutes. I'll
get it prepared by then.
この俺にイカサマ勝負を挑むとは
バカな野郎どもだ。
These fools want to take me on in
a battle of cheaters? Bring it on.
ハハハ…。
くーっ！こんなキツい
エクササイズやらせんなよ！
Don't make me do such tiring exercises!
そんなんじゃ
東条に置いてかれちまうぞ。
If not, you'll get left in the dust by Tojo.
東条？
Tojo?
ああ。あいつも　あの連中と
一戦交えたらしくてな。→
Yeah. He was caught up in
a fight with those guys.
ボッコボコにやられてひでえツラしてたよ。
負けたのか？
He was beat to a pulp... Looked like crap.
He lost?
あん？そりゃそうだろ。あんまり
ひどいツラしてるもんだから→
Huh? Well, yeah.
After getting beat that bad, he asked
me to teach him how to fight Demons.
見かねて　悪魔との戦い方
教えてやるつったんだが→
あの野郎　さわりだけ聞いて
どっか行っちまいやがった。
But that bastard went off somewhere...
《東条が…》
Tojo?
ま　アイツに関しちゃ
大して心配してねえ。
Well, I ain't that worried about him.
ほっときゃ勝手に強くなるような
奴だからな。だが…問題はお前だ。
He's the kind of guy that just
gets stronger on his own.
But the problem is you.
何せ背負ってるのは魔王だ。ここらでしっかり→
See that on your back? It's a Demon Lord.
I've got to teach you how to
use that power properly now.
力の使い方を教えとかなきゃ
なんねえ。同じ契約者としてな。
You're a contract holder, like me.
ま　さくさく次のステップ行くぜ。
Now then, let's hurry
right up to the next step.
邦枝のじ～さんが　しっかり基礎を固めてくれたみて～だからな。
It looks like Kunieda's grandpa
beat the basics into you already.
邦枝のじじいとも知り合いって
マジで何もんなんだよ　てめえ。
You know Kunieda's grandpa
too? Who are you, seriously?
（早乙女）
そうだな。次の課題をクリア
できたら　教えてやってもいいぜ。
Yeah, true... If you clear the
next subject, I'll tell you.
ダーバ。
次の課題？
The next subject?
実はこいつは　昔　俺が
修業に使ったもんでな。
Actually I used this guy to
train myself in the past.
ただのラジカセじゃねえ
魔界で作られたもんだ。
This isn't your normal boombox.
It's from the Demon World.
魔界？どうりで
古くさいデザインと思ったら…。
The Demon World?
I did notice it was seriously old school.
こいつには　録音した声の主を
実体化する機能があってな。
It has the ability to turn the owner of the
voice it records into a physical being.
おい　まさか？
Wait, you don't mean...
そう。これから　お前らには
お前ら自身と戦ってもらう。
That's right. From now on,
you'll be fighting yourself.
こ　こいつは！？
ニョーダッ！
That's...
（黒ベル坊）○×□△…。
おいおい…
こんなんと戦えってか？
Wait, hold it. I'm supposed to fight this?
言っとくけど　ベル坊１人の時とかセミにすら勝てねえんだぞ。
Just so you know, but Baby Beel
can't even beat a cicada on his own.
ラジカセの前にいたせいで→
It recorded the baby's voice
because it was louder,
赤ん坊の声の方が
デカく録音されてたか。
だが　そいつが弱いとは限らんぞ。
but that doesn't mean he's weak.
（黒ベル坊）マーッ！
ううっ！！
何せ　録音した声の主の潜在能力をそのまま引き出すからな。
Why? Because it draws out the hidden
power in the voice it recorded.
マジ…かよ…。
Seriously?!
（黒ベル坊）○×□△…。
《来るのか！？》
Is he coming for us?
マッ！
マッ…☆○×□△…！
なんか…呪いの言葉　雄叫びながら走ってったぞ？
Um, I think it just said some
curse words and took off.
おい　ど～すんだ！？あいつ
魔王の力そのまま使えんだろ？
Hey, what should I do? He can use
his full Demon Lord powers, right?
え　えっと～…。
Um...
バカヤロウ！何してる！追え！！なんつ～無責任な！
Idiot, what are you doing?! After him!
Take some responsibility, damn you!
○×□△…。
お　いたいた！
There he is!
おいコラ！
てめえの相手は　こっち…。
Hey! Your opponent is right here!
（黒ベル坊）○×☆△…。
飛んだぁ！？ウダーッ！？
He flew!
じ…自由すぎる…。
He can just do whatever.
おい　ベル坊！お前も飛んでみろ。ダッ…ダッ…。
Come on, Baby Beel! You try and fly!
大丈夫だ！気合いだ　気合い！！
Don't worry! Do it with guts!
ダーッ！
アダダダ…！！
うわっ！
本気にすんなよ。
オオーッ…。
Don't actually try that!
つ～か　マジか…？
この穴　底が見えねぇ…。
But damn... I can't see
the bottom of this hole.
面白れぇ…
ちょっとヤル気　出てきたぜ！
ダーッ！！
Cool...
I'm gettin' a little motivated here!
Who's left alive?
生き残ってるのは？
（アバター：ラミア）
もう　私とアンタだけよ！
It's just you and me!
How'd this happen?
なんで　そんな事に！？
あれよ！
It's that!
ああ！！ぶっ壊されたはずの
クレイジーフロッグ？
That's the Crazy Frog! I
thought it was destroyed!
Looks like they fixed it.
（アバター：ラミア）
直して使ってるみたいね。
Can cheating let you do anything?!
（アバター：古市）何でもありかよ
チートってのは！
I bet it's not just hacking the program...
たぶん　ただの
プログラム改造じゃないわ…。
I can sense a bit of magic power.
わずかに魔力を感じる。
それって…。
Then, that means...
If I were taking bets, I'd say this
is the work of a Demon Maidservant.
十中八九　侍女悪魔の仕業。
This is seriously bad, for real.
ちょっと
本気でマズいわね　これ…。
Hey, are you saying if we
lose we all die for real?!
《おいおい…負けたら全員
リアルで死んじまうんだぞ…》
What are you people doing?
何をやってんだ？お前ら。
This is where the bodies of those
people who got killed in the game go.
このコーナーは
ゲームでやられた奴らが座る→
死体置き場っス。
姫川　スマン。
Himekawa, I'm sorry. It was
just too great a burden for me.
やはり俺には
荷が重かったようだ…。
With Tanimura the medic killed too,
they can't return to the game.
衛生兵の谷村もやられちゃって
ゲームに戻れなくてさぁ。
Stop spouting this nonsense
and get back to your seats.
バカな事やってないで
席に戻れ。反撃すっぞ。
Time for our counterattack.
Counterattack?
反撃？
（姫川）ああ。→
Yeah. Took a lot of cash, but we're all set.
ずいぶん散財したが
準備オーケーだ。
This might be really something to see...
こっから先は
ちょっと見ものだぜ。
だが俺たち　もう死んでるぞ？
But, we're already dead.
Whatever! Get back in your seat, dumbass!
いいから
席に着け　タコ！
Hey, explain what's going on.
おいコラ！
何やるか説明しろ。
（姫川）向こうが透明人間なら
こっちはアンデッド…。
If they're invisible,
then we'll be the undead.
地獄のゾンビだ。
Hell zombies.
待たせたな。
ああ　そうだ。始めてくれ。
Sorry about the wait.
Yes, that's right. Begin.
As you wish.
（部長）わかりました…。
ウフッ　あ～楽しい。
Ah, wonderful! Being invisible is the best!
透明になるのって　ホント最高！
ねえ　焔王坊っちゃ…ま？
Isn't that right, Lord... En?
ブーッ…。そうじゃの～。
I'm just watching so I can't be sure,
but I bet it feels great. For you.
余は見てただけで
よう分からんが→
きっとそれは　とても
気持ちいい事なんじゃろうの～。
あらあらら～？
Isabella, don't you think we
should let him head to the front?
イザベラ。そろそろ前線に
出してあげて　いいんじゃない？
坊っちゃま
ぶんむくれちゃってるじゃな～い。
The Master is getting pouty.
ぶんむくれてないもん！
I am not pouty!
True... Okay then.
そうですね…判りました。
ほ　本当か？イザベラ！
Really, Isabella?!
However... I shall accompany you!
ただし…私もご一緒します。
Look, Master... There's your marks!
（アバター：ヨルダ）いましたよ　坊っちゃま。カモですわ。
（アバター：焔王）うむ！
Yeah!
Don't worry. They can't see us like this.
（アバター：イザベラ）大丈夫。こちらの姿は
見えておりません。→
Carefully sneak up to them, and make
sure to shoot them in the head.
落ち着いて　ゆっくり近づき
頭を確実に撃ち抜いて下さい。
Yeah, watch me! I'll show them what for!
（アバター：焔王）
よ　よ～し！見ておれ。
ギャフンと言わせてやるわい！
"What for" again?
またギャフンって…。だから　言わないって…。
Don't say anything.
フフ…気づいとらんのう！
They don't notice me!
Huh? What happened to the invisibility?
何これ　透明化が…？
Master!
坊っちゃま！
ん？
（ゾンビ：神崎）見ぃ～つけたぁ～！
Found you!
ギャ…ギャフーン！？
What the...?!!
あ　言った…。
ギャフンだよ。
Oh, he said it.
Well, close enough.
Master!
（２人）坊っちゃま～！？
I thought we'd killed that guy!
あいつ　殺したはずの奴じゃ！？どうして！？
How?!
（ゾンビ：由加）さっきは　よくもぉ…→
How dare you kill me before!
殺してくれたっスねぇ～？
ぎゃああぁぁ！？
ゾンビ！？
A zombie?!
ウキャキャキャキャ！
マジ効かね～っスよぉ～！！
Crazy, yo!
ゾンビ踵落とし
食らうかぁ～！？
Chew on a zombie heel drop!
ぎゃあぁ～！
お化け！悪魔ぁぁ～！！
Monster! Demon!
いや　悪魔は私達ですって。
Um, we're the Demons.
What's happening?
何が起きてるの？
向こうもプログラムを書き換えたようね。
Looks like they rewrote
the program themselves!
This high a level?
って　そういうレベル！？
You bought them out?
買い取った？
ああ。
Yeah. I bought the entire
game from the sales company.
このゲーム自体を
運営会社から買い取った。
If I cheat, I ain't gonna go small time.
この俺がチートなんて
セコい真似するかよ。
これで　設定いじり放題だぜ。
Now we can change the setting all we want!
っていうか　いくらで？
Um, how much did this cost?
（鳥のさえずり）
Where is this?
（邦枝）ここが…。
This is called the inner temple.
（諌冬）奥の院と
呼ばれている場所です。
But even disciples can't
enter here, let alone guests.
（邦枝）でも　ここって
一般客どころか→
許可がないと修業の人でも入れないんじゃ？
Don't worry, I told Father.
大丈夫です。
お父さんにも言ってあるから。
Tengu Daimei Shrine
I have a strange feeling...
何だか不気味な感じ…。
I don't really know how
to dispel Demons myself,
悪魔の祓い方とか　私も
本当は　よくわからないんだけど→
but there's a person here I want you to meet.
ここに会わせたい人がいるの。
A person I should meet?
会わせたい人？
Um, not exactly a person...
あ　いえ　人っていうか…→
But I think it'll definitely
help you out, Aoi-chan.
でも　きっと葵ちゃんの力に
なってくれると思うから。
あ…？ん…？
Is that person... Beel-chan?
その人って　ベルちゃん？いえ　違います…。
No, that's not it!
（鼻歌）
But, he seems to be inviting us.
でも　なんか誘ってるわよ？
Wait... Doesn't his color seem off?
というか
色おかしくないですか？
Move it, Kunieda!
どいてろ　邦枝！
Oga?
男鹿？
ダーブッ！
えっ！？そっちもベルちゃん？
Beel-chan's over there, too?
That bastard keeps runnin' away!
この野郎！
ちょこまか逃げやがって…。
Chasing him up and down mountain paths?
Do you know how tough that is?!
山道追っかけるのが
どんだけキツいか…。
って　もういねぇ！？
なんて落ち着きのねぇ…。
And he's gone! The bastard
just won't stay still!
Where does he get that from?
誰に似たんだ！
ダーウーッ！！
"Da" my ass! It's you!
ダーじゃねえ！お前だよ！！
Wait, Oga! Why are there two Beel-chans?
ちょ　ちょっと　男鹿！
なんでベルちゃんが２人いるの？
Explain!
ねえ！？
ん？待てよ…
ベル坊に似てるって事は…。
Wait... If he's like Baby Beel, then...
ヘッ！余裕ぶっこいてられんのも今のうちだ。
Just keep on shakin' it... While you can!
ベル坊！
ダッ！！
Baby Beel!
ダンッ！
ダ～～～ッ…→
Bunny
ダピョン！
オウ？
ダピョン　ダピョン　ダピョン…。
○☆□×…！
☆○×△…！
Bingo!
ビンゴ！
（ゾンビ：城山）ゲボアァァ！
Isabella-sama, no matter
how much we shoot them...
イザベラ様！
こいつら撃っても撃っても…。
ひぃ！！
...our attacks don't work at all!
攻撃が効きませぇ～ん！
（ゾンビ：寧々）ヒヒヒヒヒ～！！
What's happening?
どうしたのじゃ！？
あの役立たず共が…。
The useless fools...
What does it matter, as
long as we're still around?
構わないじゃない
私達が残ってれば。
大丈夫なのか？
Will we be okay?
Even if they're zombies,
they can't beat this robot!
（アバター：サテュラ）
それに　いくらゾンビでも
このロボには勝てね～っすよ。
（ガシャン！）
（一同）ん？
Don't underestimate me, asswipes!
ナメてんじゃね～ぞ　ボケが。→
そんなもん…→
Did you seriously...
...think you could win with only one?
たった１機で
勝てると思ってんのかよ？
No way!
（一同）うっそぉぉ～ん！
Let's go!
行くぜ！
（４人）おう！！
Right!
Ultimate Delinquent Combination!
（石矢魔一同）超絶不良合体！！
Bow down before Maximum King Ishiyama!
（石矢魔一同）見参！→
マックス・デ・イシヤマオー！
Maximum King Ishiyama
Ultimate Delinquent Combination
Let's do this!
やるぜぇ～っ！
（石矢魔一同）超必殺！！
Super Special Attack!
いや！ちょっと待ちなさい！？
私達の負け負け負け～！！
W-Wait a second! We give up, we give up!
Diamond Evil Arrow!
（石矢魔一同）
ダイヤモンド　エビル　アローッ！
We won!
（一同）勝ったぁ～っ！
Okay, I won!
よぉ～し　勝ったぁ～！
As I thought, he's as stupid as Baby Beel!
やっぱ知能はベル坊並だな。
ダピョン　ダピョン…。
Come on, Baby Beel! Give 'em a kick!
おい　ベル坊。
お前も蹴りとか入れてやれ！
ダピョン　ダピョン…。
That's fun?
って　楽しくなってる！？
ま　いいや…。
Whatever... Anyway, training...
とりあえず
これで修業は…ん？
Flip tape. Flip tape.
（ラジカセの声）
テープ反転　テープ反転。→
Changing to side B.
これよりＢ面に変わります。
（早乙女）フゥ…始まったか。
And so it begins.
ぐっ…！！
ダブ？
何だ…？
What the...
アー？
This guy is...
こいつ…！？
ダブーッ！？
（パキッ…）
（ヒルダ）むっ…。
不吉な…。
A bad omen...
I have a bad feeling about this.
何やら嫌な予感がする…。
Perhaps I should go to the Master's side...
私も　そろそろ
坊っちゃまの元へ行くべきか…。
Lonely...
寂しい…。
Go, Ultimate Delinquent Combination:
Maximum King Ishiyama!
Enough with games. I'm joining in.
I'll have a direct showdown
with Yolda and the others.
Hilda-san, we've been waiting!
Let's combine together!
I said enough of that!
Anyway, you take care of Lamia, Furuichi.
Yeah, well combining with
kids ain't my thing.
On the next Beelzebub: Sorry
to Have Kept You Waiting.
Finally, a serious battle between
Hilda-san and Yolda-san!
Who will win? Plus, what the hell
is Oga doing this whole time?